Guide to the Kathleen Hanna Papers MSS.271
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Media
  - Subseries B: Video - Originals
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ 12, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0150)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 2005 9:30 Club DC (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0151)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 - Sony 1 - Amsterdam (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0152)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 - Sony 2 - Gothenburg, SE (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0153)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 1 - Behind-the-scenes- Amsterdam, Hamburg, Conan O'Brien (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0154)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 2 - Amsterdam - Paradiso Show (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0155)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 3 - Fabrik Hamburg, G (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0156)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 4 - Tragdam Festival; Gothenborg, Sweden (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0157)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 5 - Umea, SE (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0158)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 6 - 4.11.05 Copenhagen, D L: Camera R: Mono board mix (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0159)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 7 - 4.13 Berlin, G Club M (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0160)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 1 - Gravy Train Bus, Bus Dance Party! (LA), Plant, Showers, McRorie, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0161)
    - LT [Le Tigre] SUM '05 2 - Bugs!, JD Pose w/car, JD drunk, Feminist Parking Lot! (In), 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0162)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 3 - 8.4.2011 Exit/In Nahsville, TN, L: Board, R: Mic, SR Pos, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0163)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 4 - Fem Park Lot Pt. II (IN), 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0164)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 5 - 9.6.05 Peabody's, Clev, Ohio Board Mix Only Center Pos., 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0165)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 6 - Chicago Show, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0166)
    - Le Tigre - 9/18/05 Crowd interviews, Webster Hall, NYC, 24p camera, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0167)
    - Le Tigre 9/18/05 Line @ Webster Hall, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0168)
    - Le Tigre 9/18/05 Le Tigre - Webster Hall F.O.H. - Topiary, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0169)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 9/18/05 Web Hall -Bob-, 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0170)
    - "Le Tigre" Webster Hall 9/18/05 (wide shot), 2005 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0171)
    - Stage L WS. 9/18 Webster Hall, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0172)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Operation Peace, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0173)
    - Le Tigre video 2005 Green Screen Cake (Kol) (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0174)
    - Le Tigre 2 - Oh No - The Cat! * Le Tigre Stuff Green Screen: Gina, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0175)
    - Le Tigre 9/18 NYLA, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0176)
    - Le Tigre 9/18 NYLA, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0177)
    - LT [Le Tigre] DUO Yoshi Footage, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0178)
    - Eugene Photage, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0179)
    - [untitled 1 of 2], undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0180)
    - [untitled 2 of 2], undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0181)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Johanna 1 1/20/10 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0182)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Johanna 2 1/20/10 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0183)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Kathleen 1/20/10 intv (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0184)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Kathleen 2 1/20/10 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0185)
    - LT [Le Tigre] LD 1/22/10, 2010 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0186)
    - LT [Le Tigre] LD 2 1/22/10, 2010 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0187)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 1/22/10 3 way 1 3 shot, 2010 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0188)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 3 way 2 3 shot, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0189)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 1/22/10 3 way closeups 1, 2010 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0190)
    - LT [Le Tigre] close ups 2, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0191)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 3 way close ups 3, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0192)
    - VHS Dub le Tigre / Bikini Kill 1, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0193)
    - VHS Dub le Tigre / Bikini Kill 2, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0194)
    - VHS Dub le Tigre / Bikini Kill 3, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0195)
    - Bikini Kill - Sanctuary Theater, April 4, 1992 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0196)
      Format: [DVD-R]
    - BK 072592, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0197)
      Format: DVD-R
    - Bikini Kill - Capitol Building - Washington, DC, July 25, 1992 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0198)
    - Bikini Kill - Possibly Joe Hunter - Washington, DC, May 29, 1992 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0199)
    - Kathleen Hanna Spoken Word - International Pop Underground, August 22, 1991 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0200)
    - Bikini Kill? - Girl Day - IPU, Olympia, WA, Aug 20, 1991 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0201)
    - Bikini Kill - Wetlands, NY3, May 3, 1992 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0202)
    - Three Dollar Bill, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0203)
    - Bikini Kill - Wetlands, May 3, 1992 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0210)
    - Le Tigre Live Performances to be used for INT. Multiclip Sequences as of 1.14.10, January 14, 2010 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0211)
    - Anti-war DC show (bad audio) video, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0212)
    - Washington International School - 10th Grade Talent Show Students Performing Le Tigre's "Deceptacon", March 2004 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0215)
      from Le Tigre Memories Box 3 Folders 4-6
    - Le Tigre DVD Extras: songs [1 of 2], undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0216)
    - Le Tigre DVD Extras: songs [2 of 2], undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0217)
  - Subseries C: Audio - Access Copies
    Audio materials have not been preserved and are not available to researchers.
  - Subseries D: Audio - Originals
    - My Metrocard, RED SPEEDWAGON (just like), Not Gold REDO, Soldierboy, long keyboard thing do the do the do the [Bagious], Jurassic (F. Mashine version), undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0109)
      Format: 1/4"
    - Side One: Bikini Kill Live North Shore Surf Club Olympia, WA 2/14/91 Bratmobile 4 songs; Side Two: More Bikini Kill (2 songs), Folk Artists (Audio Lab) 1) Kayta 2) Christine, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0110)
    - Viva Knievel, 1st 3 15ips, 2nd 2 7.5, 1/4 track, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0111)
    - VIVA KNEIVEL, Side A: Dog, Calvinator; Side B: Boy Poison, Die Vermin, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0112)
    - Crochet #1, Crochet #2 gets cut off, Virginia Slims, Tanya, Delicious, Organ Inst., Jo-Jo, Fuck you, 4-track Stay Monkey doubtful version, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0113)
    - Wish list, Mental Health Questionaire, My morning is summer, Tania #2, Crochet #2, Fun machine take one, Hot Hot Summer, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0114)
    - A Place called I won't be there, Radical or Pro Parental, Song for Nikki, I wanna know what <3 is, Make out Song, Luv Song, What the Rich are Doing, Factory Sunshine, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0115)
    - The Pat, Record over me!, No word yet, Jurassic, I want it too LT, new stop starts one, GET ELECTRIC, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0116)
    - Giant ass of Man collaboration with MRP, My My metrocard needs vocals, guitar, keyboards, Disco Disco Dick (Boy Version), DO Right, test for Les + Ray, Les + Ray, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0117)
    - (misfire of the braces) Trevor #2 (Bring it on), undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0118)
    - Julie Ruin Vgi: vgi, Hot Hot Summer in Hell, Dear John, new slow song s(posed) to be machine <- not u sing this, punk song, Doghouse, Beautiful World, undated (Box 14, Media 271.0119)
    - Hallie Ruth, Kathleen Hanna 2 Loops, x lesley gore loop > stay monkey x cares loop > Breakout H-town, more Hallie Ruth, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0120)
    - le tigre: Any Day Now Loop Communique, get electric, the the empty, Hurry up, Locness Medussa, Amnesia, The The Empty, Get Electric, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0121)
    - Weird thing me + Adam did, eau d'bedroom dancing, Altruism, Apt #5, Disco Disco Dick, New Fastish one, completely, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0122)
    - Mediocrity Rules, Bang! Bang!, Call It, MY ART, gone bt yr home #1, gone bt yr home #2, Song for Molly, My 2nd Loop, Keep on Livin, Cabbie with Drums, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0123)
    - Cumberland Arms, Byker, Newcastle, England, April 17, 1996 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0204)
      Format: CD-R
    - Democrazy, Ghent, Belgium, April 14, 1996 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0205)
    - Capitol Theater, Olympia, WA, December 9, 1994 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0206)
    - Jabberjaw, Los Angeles, July 6, 1994 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0207)
    - Pavilion Theatre, Brighton, England, March 18, 1993 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0208)
    - Tinuviel's Phoenix House, Olympia, April 13, 1991 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0209)
    - Le Tigre - Nagoya, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0213)
    - Le Tigre - Budakon, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0214)
    - Katie Agresta Vocal Studios Inc, undated (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0218)
      From Le Tigre Memories
      Format: audiocassette
    - Le Tigre - Hot Topic, 1999 (Box 14, Media ID: 271.0219)
      Format: 7"
    - Julie Ruin, Julie Ruin, 1997 (Box Shared Fales 046, Folder 1)
  - Subseries E: Video - Submasters - CLOSED
    CLOSED
    - Bikini Kill 10/10/94-Funk Shop, Ft. Collins Co., undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0055)
      Source ID
      271.0005
    - Bikini Kill, Haltam City, TX, 11/12/94, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0058)
      271.0006
    - Stupid Punx, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0075)
      271.0019
    - Le Tigre, Metro Daily Beat, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0081)
      271.0023
    - Girl Speak - at UC Irvine, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0084)
      271.0024
    - Geffen Music Video, Sonic Youth "Bull in the Heather", undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0086)
      271.0025
    - A Video by Corin Tucker with Bikini Kill; etc., undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0098)
      271.0029
    - The Judy Spots, Sadie Benning, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0069)
      271.0010
    - Getting Close to Nothing, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0072)
      271.0018
    - Viva Knievel "Good Girl Bad Dog', 1200 Seconds, Slim Moon "Poor Man's Parnassus", undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0089)
      271.0026
    - Bikini Kill, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0092)
      271.0027
    - Dub B-K, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0095)
      271.0028
    - 5/9 Guilty; Bikini Kill, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0101)
      271.0030
    - A Show of Appreciation for: Johanna, JD, and Kathleen; etc..., undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0104)
      271.0031
    - Kathleen MTV News, undated (Box Shared Fales PM 12, Case 271.0107)
      271.0032
  - Subseries F: Video - Preservation Masters - CLOSED
    - ID: 271.0033 (Box Shared Fales PM 64)
    - ID: 271.0036 - 271.0074 (Box Shared Fales PM 65)
    - ID: 271.0077 - 271.0083, 271.0088 - 271.0106 (Box Shared Fales PM 66)
- Series IV: Computer Disks
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Just the facts ma'am - Le Tigre web content - For Stella simpletext, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.3.0001)
    From [Le Tigre] Website Originals Box 3 Folder 7.
  - K. Hanna - from the desk of...jpegs, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.3.0002)
  - MASTA, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.3.0003)
  - Le Tigre stuff 4 Stella, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.3.0004)
  - From the Beds + Letters show - Lesbian Beds Tammy Rae Carland, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.3.0005)
    From Gallery Stuff [3 of 3] Box 2 Folder 3
- Series V. 2015 Accretion
  Scope and Contents
  This accretion consists of a dvd on the Riot grrrl movement, an exhibition program, and newspaper and magazine articles related to Kathleen Hanna and/or Bikini Kill.
  - Revolution Riot Grrrl Style, 2014
    - Analog Copy (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Digital Copy, FA_MSS_271_ER_1
  - "Many Woods" Exhibition Program, 1988-06-02 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Articles, 1988-2015 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Filing Cabinet Files
  Oversize Series I: Filing Cabinet: This series consists of oversize materials removed from Series I for preservation reasons. The folder titles of oversize materials are the same as the folders they were removed from.
  - Friends' Work [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 1, Folder 16)
  - Spoken Word [Fringe Festival poster], undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bikini Kill/ Riot Grrrl Memorabilia [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Resume [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - [Riot Grrrl Zines/ Flyers] [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - April Fool's Day #1 [zine master] [1 of 2], [1995] (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - April Fools Day #1 [zine master] [2 of 2], [1995] (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Reject All American LP Sleeve, [1996] (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 3-D FreAk VolCAno group art show [poster], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Gallery stuff [felt banner], undated (Flat-file-folder 4R)
  - Things I made [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Julie Ruin Press Kit/One Sheets [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Julie Ruin Album Art Mock-Ups, 1997 (Box Shared Fales 093)
  - Le Tigre Press [New York Times Article with color photo of Ric Oscasek], 2004 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Le Tigre Memories [posters], undated (Box 16, Folder 13)